const quizQuestions = [
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-1",
    question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    a: "React doesn't return element",
    b: "1 Element",
    c: "More than 1 element",
    d: "None of the mentioned",
    isCorrect: "b",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-2",
    question: "Which of the following JavaScript cannot do ?",
    a: "JavaScript can react to events",
    b: "JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements",
    c: "JavaScript can be use to validate data",
    d: "All of the Above",
    isCorrect: "d",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-3",
    question: "How can you created rounded corners using CSS3 ?",
    a: "border[round]: 30px;",
    b: "corner-effect: round;",
    c: "border-radius: 30px;",
    d: "alpha-effect: round-corner;",
    isCorrect: "c",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-4",
    question: "What does RGBa mean ?",
    a: "Review Get assistance Back-up your information acquire proof",
    b: "Red Green Blue alpha",
    c: "Red Gray Brown alpha",
    d: "Red Gold Black alpha",
    isCorrect: "b",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-5",
    question: "What ReactJs cover ?",
    a: "User Interface layer in an application",
    b: "Data layer in an application",
    c: "Both A and B",
    d: "None of the above",
    isCorrect: "a",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-6",
    question:
      "Which of the following is used to specify the subscript of text using CSS?",
    a: "vertical-align: sub",
    b: "vertical-align: super",
    c: "vertical-align: subscript",
    d: "None of the above",
    isCorrect: "a",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-7",
    question:
      "Which of the following are the CSS Extension Prefixes for Webkit?",
    a: "-chrome",
    b: "-web",
    c: "-o-",
    d: "-webkit",
    isCorrect: "d",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-8",
    question: "To show deleted text, which HTML element is used?",
    a: "<del>",
    b: "<em>",
    c: "<strong>",
    d: "<ins>",
    isCorrect: "a",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-9",
    question:
      "Which character is used to represent when a tag is closed in HTML?",
    a: "#",
    b: "!",
    c: "/",
    d: "None",
    isCorrect: "c",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-10",
    question:
      "Which of the following elements in HTML5 defines video or movie content?",
    a: "<video>",
    b: "<movie>",
    c: "<audio>",
    d: "<media>",
    isCorrect: "a",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-11",
    question: "Which object in Javascript doesn't have a prototype?",
    a: "Base Object",
    b: "All objects have a prototype",
    c: "None of the objects have a prototype",
    d: "None of the above",
    isCorrect: "a",
  },
  {
    quesNumber: "Q-12",
    question: "Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?",
    a: "Date",
    b: "File Upload",
    c: "Function",
    d: "All of the above",
    isCorrect: "d",
  },
];

export { quizQuestions };
